[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the human body does the science periodontics study?", "correct_answer": "Gums and mouth", "incorrect_answers": ["Eyes", "Finger and toes", "Ears"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie star said the following words: I had to break up with him because he had an incurable disease. I didnt know it was stupidity!?", "correct_answer": "Sandra Bullock in Miss Congeniality", "incorrect_answers": ["Meg Ryan in Youve got mail!", "Susan Sarandon in Thelma and Louise", "Michelle Pfeiffer in Grease 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Janis Ian hate Regina George in the comedy movie Mean Girls?", "correct_answer": "Regina started a rumor that Janis was a lesbian.", "incorrect_answers": ["Janis wished she was the queen bee instead of Regina.", "Regina said Janis had slept with the entire football team.", "Regina was rich, and made fun of how poor Janis was."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The scarab, a sacred beetle to Ancient Egyptians, is commonly known as what?", "correct_answer": "Dung Beetle", "incorrect_answers": ["Stag Beetle", "June Bug", "Noble Chafer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie My Big Fat Greek Wedding come out?", "correct_answer": "2002", "incorrect_answers": ["2003", "2001", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many square yards are there in an acre of land?", "correct_answer": "4,840", "incorrect_answers": ["4,350", "4,520", "4,130"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of meat is traditionally used for the preparation of the Vietnamese soup called Pho?", "correct_answer": "Beef", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabbit", "Pork", "Snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unit is used in the metric system for measuring time?", "correct_answer": "the second", "incorrect_answers": ["the Ohm", "the grad", "the cell phone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first ever Calvin Klein collection featured what kind of clothes?", "correct_answer": "Coats", "incorrect_answers": ["Hats", "Underwear", "T-shirts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Ted Kramer in the 1979 Oscar-winning drama movie Kramer vs. Kramer?", "correct_answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Penn", "Anthony Hopkins", "Christopher Walken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Cody Jarrett die in the 1949 crime movie White Heat?", "correct_answer": "He kills himself.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is shot dead.", "In a car accident.", "His mother stabs him to death."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a classic scene from the Rambo quadrilogy, Rambo kills a guy in a helicopter with a rock. In which Rambo movie does this take place?", "correct_answer": "First Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["First Blood pt. II", "Rambo III", "Rambo"]}]